





Profile

I have been a creative person my entire life and love to dedicate myself to the entire creative process. Film and Video Editor/Graphic Designer adept in meeting client needs throughout the entirety of the film and design process including working with clients from conception to completion to ensure that videos and designs are everything they hoped for. Able to handle a variety projects providing the highest level of service, quality, and innovation. Experienced in editing film for commercials, special events, youtube, individual client personal needs, logos, advertising and brand conceptualizing.

Employment History

Freelancer

February 2021 — Present

- Creating various youtube video for clients based on specific channel
- · Creating logos and brand identity

Video Editor/Graphic Designer, The Art Institute of Fort Lauderdale

July 2017 — October 2019

- Worked one-on-one with clients and various department members to meet their film editing needs.
- Maintained serious focus and met strict deadlines with ease.
- Converted hours of raw footage into final products.
- Used computer editing equipment and a host of creative techniques to achieve desired layout and style.
- Implemented high-quality sound effects, voices, and music seamlessly into videos.
- Maintaining client's relationship with constant open dialogue and good communication skills
- Designing posters and advertisements for clients while also promoting said advertisements
- Creating logos from concept to final design
- Constructing advertisement for events
- Prepares illustrations and rough sketches of material, discussing them with clients and making necessary changes

Education

Associate of fine arts in graphic design, The Art Institute of Fort Lauderdale July 2016 — October 2019

References

References available upon request

Adobe Premiere Pro Adobe After Effects Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator Design Applications

Links

Illustration

Portfolio